（忆往昔）
蒂塔妮亚之翼
Wings of Titania,
让我开启天眼
bear mine eyes aloft as I bid thee…
- 巫术袋 - 所以是女巫
- Hex bag. - So we're thinking witch?
是古老的黑魔法
Yeah. This is old-world black magic.
我们是来找这个女巫的 罗威娜
We're here for the witch. Rowena.
母亲
Mother?
你可抛弃了我三百年
You did manage to stay away for 300 years.
我跟大巫师团闹僵了
There was the unpleasantness with the Grand Coven.
那种环境根本不适合带孩子
It was no environment for a child!
- 他偷什么了 - 花生酱和面包
- So, what did he take? - Peanut butter and bread.
他们送我去了个男童院
They sent me to a boys' home.
我教你服从纪律 承担责任 迪恩
Teaches you some discipline and responsibility, Dean.
让你不去惹麻烦
Keep you out of trouble.
- 是该隐 - 该隐和亚伯那个吗
- It's cain. - As in Cain and Abel?
路西法要把我弟弟变作他的宠物
Lucifer was gonna make my brother into his pet.
所以我提出了协议
And so I offered a deal …
这可是该隐的血印
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
我变成了地狱的战士
So I became a soldier of hell …
我能给你那个血印 迪恩 如果你真想如此
I can give you the mark, Dean, if it's what you truly want.
但你得清楚这个血印会给你的重担
But you have to know with the mark comes a great burden.
搞什么 查理
What the hell? Charlie?
我们的身体还有联系
We're still connected physically.
如果你们伤害她 也会伤到我
If you hurt her, you hurt me.
迪恩
Dean!
我很抱歉 丫头
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
我原谅你了 迪恩
I forgive you, Dean.
你还好吧
You good?
不好
No.
（如今）
（俄勒冈州 彭德尔顿）
不是我啊 我没拿
It wasn't me, man! I didn't take it!
你总跑来偷我东西
You keep on coming and stealing from me!
不是…
It was that…
钱哪去了 我的钱哪去了
Where's my money? Where's my money?!
把钱还给我
You give me my money!
我以我老妈起誓 JP
Swear on my mother, J.P.,
再让我在这儿看到你
I see your face in here again…
我杀了你
I'll kill you.
去你的
Like hell.
这可是美国 你不能…
This is freakin' America, man. You can't just…
看什么看
What you looking at?
[邪恶力量 第10季第12集]
该隐杀了亚伯之后 他成了恶魔
After Cain killed Abel, he became a demon.
我从一开始就觉得我们心有灵犀
I felt connected to you right from the beginning.
我们很像
You and I are very much alike.
我能给你那个血印 迪恩 如果你真想如此
I can give you the mark, Dean, if it's what you truly want.
我开杀戒是有理由的
But when I kill, I kill for a reason.
我和该隐没有半点相似之处
I'm nothing like Cain.
你为什么要抗拒自己的本性呢
Why are you fighting what you really are?
（激光除疤）
发现桩案子
Caught a case.
有什么东西在劫持人
Apparently something is taking people.
并留下他们的衣服
and leaving their clothes.
早该来个限制级的活儿了
About time this gig got an "R" rating.
好吧 你去看看吧
All right. Why don't you check it out?
我在这里留守
I'll hold down the fort.
迪恩 你已经一周没离开地堡了
Dean, you haven't left the bunker in a week.
怎么了
And?
你不能余生都
And you can't just live the rest of your life.
把自己关在这间屋子里
locked up in this room.
怎么了 我这儿有吃的有床
I don't know. I got three hots and a cot.
- 不错了 - 我知道你担心血印的事
- Could be worse. - Look, I know you're worried about the mark.
是啊 萨姆 没错
Yes, Sam. I am.
我对查理大打出手
Between what I did to Charlie…
查理原谅了你
Charlie forgave you.
你能不能原谅自己
How about you forgive yourself?
我现在的记录可不太好
Because I'm not exactly batting 1, 000 here, you know?
这我知道
Yeah, I do know that,
但关在这里 坐在地上
But staying locked up in here, sitting on the ground.
反复读同一堆传说书籍
reading the same lore books over and over and over again,
也没用啊
it's not helping you.
为了你自己 你得继续猎魔
You need to get back in the game for your own good.
你可以战胜这个的 迪恩
You can beat this, Dean.
你真相信吗
Do you really believe that?
我当然相信
Yeah, you're damn right I believe that.
你12岁之前还相信复活节兔子呢
You know, you also believed in the easter bunny till you were 12.
才没有
No, I didn't.
我那时才11
Look, I was 11.
岁半
And a half.
11岁半 好吧
And a half. Right.
怎么样
So?
好吧
Okay.
然后…一道白光
And then… then… then there was this bright light,
然后 那家伙一下就没了
and… bam… the dude's just gone.
什么都不剩
Nothing left but, uh…
只有一套便宜西装和男鞋吗
A cheap suit and a pair of florsheims?
差不多吧
Pretty much.
你看到别人了吗
You see anyone else?
没有 警官
No, sir, officer.
那有没有觉得冷
And what about, uh, a chill?
或者闻到臭鸡蛋味儿了吗
Or did you smell any rotten eggs?
什么
What?
没有
No, man. Uh…
我闻到花香了
I smelled flowers, though.
花香 什么样的花香
You smelled flowers? What kind of flowers?
就是花香
Flowery flowers.
听着
Look.
我们都清楚这其实是怎么回事
We all know what's going on here, okay?
别说
Don't say it.
外星人
Aliens.
他说了
He said it.
是啊
Yeah, he did.
那人被绑架了
Dude was abducted.
相信我 我知道的
Believe me, I know.
2003年5月 那些混蛋 他们抓走了我
May 2003. Those suckers, they grabbed me,
- 还到处捅我 - 好吧
- and they probed me everywhere. - Okay.
- 多谢配合 - 真的到处都捅遍了
- Thanks for your time. - Yeah. I'm talking everywhere.
- 到处啊 - 嗯 好
- And I mean everywhere. - Okay, okay.
- 简直扯得没边了 - 是啊
- Well, the wheels just came flying off the bus. - Yeah.
没有冷点 大概不是鬼
No cold spots means it probably wasn't a ghost.
没有硫磺 不是恶魔
And no sulfur means no demons,
那么是什么情况
so that leaves us with what?
几个小绿人 一桶润滑油吗
Couple of little green dudes and a bucket of lube?
或者仙子
Or fairies.
或者天使
Or…angels.
我倒宁可是小绿人了
I'd rather have the little green dudes.
我去JP家翻翻看
All right, I'll go scope out J.P.'s place.
你去里面打听一下
You, uh… you ask around inside.
要么
Or you know what?
我们别分开了
We don't have to split up.
不不 没事的
No, no, no. It's cool.
问当地人几个问题我还是做得来的
I can handle a little 20 questions with the locals, okay?
- 你确定吗 - 嗯 这是个酒吧
- You sure? - Yeah, hey, look, it's a dive bar.
我会如鱼得水的
It's my comfort zone, hmm?
好吧 那好
All right. Good.
太好了
Great.
要点什么
What can I do you?
去他的 我要相信自己
Screw it. I'm gonna believe in myself.
有你的
Attaboy.
给我点有劲的东西
Give me something dark and strong.
你认识那个失踪的家伙 JP吗
Hey, did you know that guy that went missing… J.P.?
谁想知道
Who's asking?
就是个老朋友
Just an old pal.
发生这种事我很遗憾
Look, I'm sorry to hear about what happened.
但 那人就是个渣滓
But… guy's a lowlife.
那晚上 我把他赶了出去 因为他偷我小费
That night, I had to kick his ass out of here for stealing my tips.
不管JP是遭遇了什么
Whatever J.P. got…
他八成是罪有应得
probably had it coming.
JP也没那么糟
J.P. wasn't that bad.
你认识他
You knew him?
我们关系没那么好 但的确认识
This isn't exactly "cheers, " but yeah.
别误会
And don't get me wrong,
我可不敢跟他买二手车
I would not buy a used car from the guy.
但他不会伤害别人
But he was harmless.
那他的问题在哪
So, what was his problem?
多了去了
What wasn't?
这么大白天在这儿买醉
You're in here getting stunned while the sun's still up,
生活肯定一团糟
your life's a regular Charlie foxtrot.
相信我
Trust me.
我是迪恩
I'm Dean.
蒂娜
Tina.
慢用
There you go.
你怎么知道斯克兰顿的皇家旅馆
How do you know the royale motel in Scranton?
我爸 我和我弟 我们被大雪困在那儿一周
My dad, me, and my bro… we got snowed in there for a week.
我在那里待了三个多月
Well, I was there for about three months.
因为我爸把我们的钱都喝光了
after my father drank all our money away.
吃白米和嘀嗒糖过活 直到被赶走
Lived on white rice and tic tacs until they kicked us out.
好时光啊
Good times.
我爸一直在工作
My dad was always working,
于是我研究出大概101种
So I came up with about 101 different ways.
做奶酪通心粉的方式
to make macaroni and cheese.
真的假的
Serious?
真的 加番茄酱当调味料
Oh, yeah. Now, add ketchup for spice, hmm?
金枪鱼 热狗
Uh, tuna, hot dogs,
还有混搭棉花糖
fluff marshmallow mix.
听上去好恶心
Ugh! That sounds disgusting.
我弟弟还觉得挺新奇
Yeah, well, my brother thought it was exotic.
敬糟糕的童年
Well, here's to, uh, crappy childhoods.
好啊
Hey. All right.
抱歉
Sorry.
我该走了
I should go.
（萨姆呼叫）
免得你无可救药地爱上我
Before you fall hopelessly in love with me.
你不会有事吧
You gonna be okay?
向来都好
I always am.
- 怎么样 - 不太好
- How we looking? - Not great.
JP再过三天就会被驱逐了
Turns out J.P. was about three days from getting evicted.
房东说他成天放尼尔·戴蒙德的歌曲
His landlord said the guy blasted Neil Diamond 24/7.
还说他的厕所是
and that his bathroom was,
「魔鬼的屁眼」
"Like staring into the devil's butt."
好生动
That's vivid.
而且准确 我看到了
And accurate. I saw it.
你看到了厕所还是…
You saw the John, or, uh…
少来
Don't.
你有发现吗
So, you got anything?
我…
Yeah. I got, uh,
什么都没发现 怎么办
Jack with two scoops of squat. I don't know, man.
我们今晚就到此为止吧
I think we ought to just call it a night and, uh…
然后呢
And what?
迪恩 喂
Dean? Hello?
萨姆 我好像有发现
Sammy, I think I got something.
蒂娜
Tina?
搞什么
What the hell?
该死
Son of a bitch.
不是吧
Seriously?
你叫什么
What's your name?
迪恩
Dean.
迪恩 是我啊 蒂娜
Dean? It's me… Tina.
什么
What?
求你告诉我你知道这是怎么回事
Please tell me you know what the hell is going on.
老实说 我还不确定
Honestly, I'm not sure yet.
我出了酒吧 然后…
Because I left the bar and then there was this…
有一道白光吗
A light? A bright light?
对 然后我就到这里了
Yes, and then I was here,
我还以为这是做恶梦 但是…
and I thought this was a nightmare, but…
天呐 如果你也在
Oh, god, if you're here…
这不可能是真的 这…
It can't be real. This doesn't…
我知道 尽量保持冷静
I know. Just try to stay calm, okay?
冷静 我变成小孩了
Stay calm? I'm a freakin' tween,
你看上去像想进单向乐队没成功的小屁孩
and you look like some One Direction reject.
而且我们在吓人的连环杀手地下室里
And we're in some freaky serial-killer basement.
- 我不能… - 蒂娜
- I can't… - Tina, Tina, just…
我不会让你有事的 好吗
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you, okay?
我不会再让你有别的事了
Well, anything else happen to you.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
你怎么这么冷静
How are you so calm?
熟能生巧
Practice.
那位是谁
Who's your friend?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
他不说话
He doesn't talk.
JP
J.P.?
不要
No!
No.
别
Don't!
这可是美国 你不能这么做
This is freakin' America, man! You can't do this!
不要
No!
（呼叫迪恩）
是什么
What is it?
伙计
Hey, buddy?
那外套哪来的
Where did that Jacket come from?
我的成人礼礼物
My bar mitzvah.
那晚上很神奇
It was a magical night.
当然了
Yeah, I bet.
再说一遍
Why don't you try it again?
垃圾箱
Dumpster.
在垃圾箱旁找到的
Found it by the dumpster.
好
All right.
他们大概下了毒
They probably poisoned it.
是啊
Right.
当然了
Obviously.
你觉得他们把JP怎么了
What do you think they're doing to J.P.?
没好事
Nothing good.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
把我们弄出去
Getting us out of here.
之前
You know, before…
我以为你就是个普通的酒鬼
I thought you were just another drunk.
我更喜欢人说行为正常酗酒者
I prefer functional alcoholic.
说真的
Seriously, who…
你是什么啊
What are you?
这…说来话长了
That… is a long-ass story.
花
Flowers.
好嘞
Yahtzee.
快走
Get out.
什么
What?
快走 我会拖住他
Hurry. I'll keep him busy.
不行 你得跟我一起来
Screw that. You're coming with me.
没时间了 快走吧 找人来帮忙
There's no time. Go. Get help.
- 蒂娜 - 我知道你能做到
- Tina… - I know you will.
救命 救命啊
Help me! Help me, please!
我需要医生
I need a doctor!
I need a doctor now!
你叫唤什么呢
What are you screaming about, girl?
（巫术和神秘学 蓍草）
你好
Yeah?
你好啊 小萨姆
Hiya, Sammy.
迪恩吗
Dean?
嗯
Yeah.
等等
W-wait a second.
你是个
Y-you're a…
怎么回事
How?
不知道
No clue.
有个疤脸 一道白光
Some scarface-looking dude, bright light.
紧接着 我醒来就变成比伯了
Next thing I know, I wake up looking like Bieber.
为什么有人要把你变成…
Why would someone turn you into…
不知道 不在乎
Don't know. Don't care.
我们有手雷吗
Hey, we got any grenades?
什么
What?
别…等等 跟我说说
Don't… wait, wait, wait. Wait a second. Talk to me.
非要现在吗 萨姆
Really, Sam? Now?
我毛都没长全 还有个姑娘命悬一线
I got no grass on the infield, and a girl's gonna die.
抱歉我现在没心情聊天
Sorry if I'm not in a chatty mood.
你想让我继续猎魔
Look, you wanted me back in the game.
我要继续猎魔了
I'm back in the damn game.
走吧
Come on.
夫人 我来吧
Ma'am, allow me.
你儿子真有礼貌
Your son is so polite.
谢了
Thanks.
- 我们去哪 - 路上说
- Where are we heading? - Tell you on the way.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
等等 或许还是我来开吧
Wait, uh… maybe I should drive?
- 好吧 - 嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
座位 座位
Okay. Seat. Seat. Seat.
蛋糕 他们给你蛋糕做什么
Cake. Why would they give you cake?
不知道
Well, don't know.
都不怎么好吃
It wasn't even good cake.
太干了
Too dry.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
好吧 是有什么 这太离奇了
Okay, not nothing. Look, this is bizarre.
就算对我们来说 迪恩 这真是疯了
Even for us, Dean. This is insane.
你差不多…多大 14岁吗
You… you're like… what, you're like 14?
是什么感觉啊
How does it even feel?
就是我自己
Well, I'm me.
心老体幼
I'm… I'm old me, but I'm a kid.
太奇怪了
It's freakin' weird, dude.
还有
And…
怎么了
What?
我去旅馆乘坐的公交车
There was a Taylor Swift song.
播了一首泰勒·斯威夫特的歌…
on the bus that I hopped to the motel, and, uh…
我好喜欢 萨姆
I liked it, Sam.
非常喜欢
Liked it a lot.
好吧
Okay.
我声音很奇怪 有9个青春痘
And my voice is weird, and I've got like nine zits,
我对这玩意毫无控制力
and I have zero control over this.
一会儿硬 一会儿软 硬得毫无理由
I mean, it's up. It's down. It's up for no reason.
够了 多谢分享
That's enough. Yeah, thanks.
这就是青春期
Uh let's just call it puberty.
是啊 糟透了 又来一次
Yeah, which sucks. Again.
听我说 我查看了你被劫走的巷子
Well, listen, I checked out the alley where you got jumped,
发现了蓍草
and I found yarrow.
什么意思
Which means what?
意味着我们面对的可能是个女巫
Means we're probably dealing with a witch.
蓍草是一种花
Yarrow's a flower.
- 在许多咒语里都会用到 - 好吧
- They use it in a ton of spells. - Okay.
我们后备箱里还有杀女巫的东西吗
We still got some of that witch-killing crap in the trunk?
当然
Hell, yeah.
等我们把你弄回来
So, we'll get you changed back,
然后烧死那个女巫
and then light Sabrina's ass up.
是吧
Right?
嗯 这个嘛
Uh, yeah, about that.
事实证明 这件怪事倒也有个好处
It turns out, this whole freak show has an upside.
血印消失了
The mark is gone.
怎么回事
How?
我觉得这个巫术
Well, I figure if this hoodoo.
如果是让我回到了14岁的时候
slammed me back into the body I had when I was 14…
你当时还没有血印
You didn't have the mark then.
如果我们逆转咒语
Yeah, and if we reverse the spell…
那血印就会回来
Then it's gonna come back.
我也这么想
That's what I'm thinking.
所以
So…
或许就别变回来了
Maybe we don't.
等等 你是想保持这副模样吗
Wait a second. Are you saying you want to stay like this?
不是啊
No.
不是 但是
No, but…
如果要在发狂的疯子禽兽
If it's between being a psycho rage monster/borderline demon.
和青少年之间选择
or a teenager, well…
不是吧
Really?
我也不喜欢 但是…
Look, I'm not a fan, either, but…
萨姆 这样问题就解决了
Sam, this is problem solved.
我还是我
And I'm still me.
我还能猎魔
I can still hunt.
我就是…嫩了一点
I'm just, you know… dewier.
好吧 你说得有点道理
Okay, look, y-you have a point, kind of,
但是 拜托…
but, dude…
是啊
I know.
有个好消息
Some good news, though…
肝脏一干二净
Virgin liver.
等我们英雄完了
So, what do you say when we're done doing our hero thing,
拿她出来练练啊
we take her for a test-drive?
好吧
Yeah, sure.
你再等…7年就能喝酒了吧
I mean…you can drink again in, what, like seven years?
不好笑
That's not funny.
- 有点好笑 - 不好笑
That's kind of funny. That's not funny.
别这样嘛 有点好笑的
Oh, come on, man. It's kind of funny.
看来有人在家
Looks like someone's home.
好 我们从地下室进去吧
Okay. Let's go in through the basement.
- 先救出蒂娜 - 好
- Get Tina out first. - All right.
还开着
Still open.
蒂娜
Tina?
好 我们走
All right, let's go.
迪恩 我块头太大进不去
Dean, I'm way too big to fit in that.
你可是第一次这么说吧
First time you ever had to say that, huh?
穿童装的人还说什么大话
Big talk coming from the dude wearing underoos.
好吧 反击得好
Okay, good one.
- 这样 你绕去后面另找进路 - 好
- Here, why don't you go around back for another way in? - Yeah.
不许动
Don't!
那女孩在哪
Where's the girl?
楼上 还活着
Upstairs. Alive.
- 你对我们做了什么 - 什么都没做
- What did you do to us? - Nothing.
我不是巫师
I'm no witch.
我只是为一个巫师工作
I just work for one.
糟糕的工作 他在哪
Crappy gig. Where is he?
是她
She.
她是全世界最糟糕的人
And she is the worst person in the world.
是这样吗
Is that so?
我已经和她在一起数个世纪了
I've been with her for centuries.
我见过她所做的事
Things I've seen her do.
我妹妹和我
My sister and I,
她逼我们伤害别人 杀害别人
she made us hurt people, kill people,
我们试图逃走时
and when we tried to escape,
她抓住了我们 折磨我
she caught us and tortured me,
然后逼我吃可怜的格莱特的心脏
and then she made me eat poor Gretel's heart.
等下 女巫 格莱特
Wait. Witch? Gretel?
怎么 你说你是…
What, are you saying that you're…
韩赛尔
Hansel.
我叫韩赛尔
My name is Hansel.
韩赛尔 还有格莱特
Hansel? And … and…and Gretel.
韩赛尔和格莱特 那个寓言故事
Hansel and Gretel, like the … like the fable.
《格林童话》里的
Like Brothers Grimm?
那不是寓言故事
It wasn't a fable.
那是根据真实事件改编的
It was based on a true story.
他们只是写了个幸福结局
They just gave it a happy ending.
好吧
Oh, okay.
我们能解决个名人 帅极了
We get to barbecue a celebrity. Cool.
你杀不了她
You can't kill her.
你们只是人
You're just men.
我们可不止
We're more than that.
我们是猎人
We're hunters.
那让我帮忙
Then let me help.
帮忙 你安得什么心
Help? What's in it for you?
因为如果你们想要干掉那糖衣贱人
Because if you're going to fry that candy-coated bitch,
我想要一起
I want in.
你想要帮忙
You want to help?
告诉我怎么把他变回来
Tell me how to turn him back.
萨姆 这事不急
Sam, it can wait.
告诉我怎么变
Tell me how!
我戴着的巫术袋
The hex bag that I'm wearing.
能够逆转咒语
It will reverse the spell.
挤一挤 你就能变回原来的年纪
Squeeze it, and you'll return to your proper age.
这样 我们解决女巫 我就给你解咒
Look, we waste the witch, I give you the cure.
成交吗
Deal?
你的朋友JP 骨头上没多少肉
Your friend J.P. Didn't have much meat on his bones.
但是好厨师会合理利用现有的食材
But a good cook works with the ingredients she's given.
好极啦
Oh. Wunderbar.
别担心 亲爱的
Oh, don't worry, liebchen.
你这么鲜嫩 做汤浪费了
You're too good for soup.
我想 好好地抹上一层辣椒
I'm thinking a nice, sweet chili glaze,
在烤箱里烤上几小时
a few hours roasting in the oven.
嘴里塞个苹果
And an apple in your mouth.
韩赛尔
Hansel.
还有我们
And pals.
走失的小羊羔啊
Well, our lost lamb.
我还以为我们得去找你
I thought we'd have to go looking for you.
甚至离开我们这个甜蜜的家
Maybe even abandon our home sweet home here.
我从没想过你会蠢到自己回来
I never dreamt you'd be stupid enough to come back on your own.
韩赛尔 拿下他们
Hansel, take care of them.
对了 他并不怎么喜欢你
Yeah, he's not exactly your biggest fan.
也许你不该强迫他吃掉他妹妹
Maybe you shouldn't have made him chow down on his sister.
我从没强迫韩赛尔做过什么
I never made Hansel do anything.
该死
Damn it!
他们是猎人
They're hunters!
[咒语]
现在 谁饿了
Now…who's hungry?
不许动
Don't move.
骨瘦如柴
Ooh. Oh, scrawny.
我们得把你喂肥点
We'll have to fatten you up.
别碰我
Don't freakin' touch me.
我要做的可不止这些
Oh, I'm going to do more than that.
小孩子
Children.
多么甜美天真
Oh, they're so sweet and innocent.
还很美味
And delicious.
你等着瞧吧
You'll see.
等我把他煮了 我会分你一点
When I cook him up, I'll give you some, hmm?
如果你这么喜欢孩子 为什么不去抓孩子
If you like kids so much, why not go after kids?
为什么要把他们变年轻
What's with this whole fountain of youth?
过去 如果孩子不见了…
Hmm, in the olden days, if a child went missing …
年轻人常会死去
Ah, the young died all the time.
不过现在 有什么安珀警报和牛奶盒
Now, though, with all your amber alerts and your milk cartons,
剁碎个小屁孩 大家都怒火冲天
a person fillets one rug rat, and people get so angry.
是啊 我说得怪奥巴马
Yeah, I blame Obama.
所以我就即兴发挥
So, I improvise.
我带走没人在乎的成年人 然后让他们返老还童
I take adults no one will miss and give them back their youth.
然后油炸了他们
And then kentucky-fry 'em.
这是我能安生吃饭的唯一办法
It's the only way I can eat in peace.
这样值得吗
So, uh, is it worth it?
据传言
I mean, word on the street is.
人尝起来就和鸡肉一样
people kind of taste like chicken.
是有点
A bit.
欧洲的孩子更像是放养的 味道更野
European children are more, uh, free-range, gamier.
不过美国的 最好吃了
Americans, though … ooh … they are heaven.
更肥
Fattier.
肉的纹理更加清晰 细嫩多汁
The meat, so finely marbled, it's almost buttery.
我就是吃不够啊
I just can't get enough.
赞极了
Mmm. Awesome.
不 我才是充满敬畏
No! I am in awe.
这是我第一次到你们国家
This is my first visit to your country,
不得不说 上帝保佑美国
and I have to say god bless the U.S.A.
那你是个游客喽
Oh, so, you're a tourist.
不是
No.
是出差 不是度假
It's business, not pleasure.
一个老朋友在惹是生非
An old friend is causing trouble,
大巫师团让我解决她
and the Grand Coven asked me to take care of her.
可怜的愚蠢的罗威娜
Poor, stupid Rowena.
等等 罗威娜
Wait. Rowena?
红发 喜欢高级酒店
She got red hair, a thing for ritzy hotels?
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
烧死你们
Now you'll burn!
待好了 小子
Stay down, boy.
转化他
Turn him!
怎么回事
The hell?
不
No!
真是太疯狂了
That was crazy.
神经病一般疯狂
Like…psycho crazy.
你们一直干这种事
And you do this all the time?
一直都是
All the freakin' time.
不是一直都这样
Not all the time.
那么
So…
你们能把我变回去吗
Can you turn me back?
巫术袋烧毁了
The hex bag went up in flames.
抱歉 蒂娜
I'm so sorry, Tina.
不过 我们也许可以逆向还原咒语
We may be able to reverse engineer the spell, though.
或许不必
Or maybe you don't.
你说什么
Come again?
我有三任前夫
I got three ex-husbands,
五万债务
50 grand in debt,
再就没什么了
and not much else.
我算是个挺糟糕的成年人
I was… kind of a crappy adult.
也许这次我能做得更好
Maybe I'll do better this time around.
离开这里 重新开始
Get out of town, get a fresh start.
这是我第二次机会
This is my second chance.
所有人都想要第二次机会 不是吗
Everybody wants a second chance, right?
你确定没问题吗
Sure you're gonna be all alght?
就像我告诉你的 向来都好
Like I told you, I always am.
至少让我们载你一程吧
Can we at least give you a ride somewhere?
钥匙给我
Give me the keys.
（俄勒冈州 彭德尔顿 大平原 大巴站）
好了 给你 这是我们所有的现金
All right, here you go. It's all the cash we got.
谢谢你们所做的一切
Thanks for everything.
要平平安安的 听到没
You stay safe out there, you hear?
我会的
I will.
我们永远还有皇家旅馆的回忆
And hey, we'll always have the Royale Motel, right?
那么…
So…
大巫师团
Grand coven.
有何想法
Any ideas?
听起来不妙
Doesn't sound good.
听起来像是金属发乐队
Well, sounds like an '80s hair-metal band.
喷很多发胶 眼影很重
You know, lot of hair spray, lot of eye shadow,
键盘吉他
lot of keytar.
不知道吗
No? Nothing?
拜托 我都给你描绘出来了
Come on, man. I'm painting a word picture here.
又回来了吗
Is it back?
我知道你要说什么
Look, I know what you're gonna say, okay?
但你当时很危险
But you were in deep.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
你救了我 救了蒂娜
You saved me, and you saved Tina,
你做了回迪恩·温切斯特
and…you pulled a Dean Winchester.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Anytime.
听着
Look, man…
我希望血印消失吗
Do I wish the mark was gone?
当然希望
Yes, of course.
绝对想 但是
Absolutely, I do, but…
我更想要你
I wanted you back.
现在你在这里
And now here you are,
你也没有发狂
and you didn't hulk out, so…
我觉得这样就够了
I'll take the win.
至于其他事
As for the rest of it …
血印 其他一切
The mark, everything else…
我们会想到办法的
…we'll figure it out.
我们一向如此
We always do.
说得对
Damn right.
我们离开这里吧
Let's get out of here.
我回来了 宝贝
I'm back, baby.